{"data":[{"question":"The bridge was hitting by a large ship during a sudden storm last week.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"was hitting","b":"during","c":"sudden","d":"last","answer":"1","explain":" - Hitting-> hit","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"The company representative sold to the manager a sewing machine for forty dollars.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"The company","b":"to the manager","c":"sewing","d":"for","answer":"2","explain":" - To the manager-> the manager","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"The taxi driver told the man to don't allow his disobedient son to hang out the window.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"taxi driver","b":"told the man","c":"to don't allow","d":"to hang out","answer":"3","explain":" - To don't allow-> not to allow","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"These televisions are quite popular in Europe, but those ones are not.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"quite","b":"in","c":"those ones","d":"are","answer":"3","explain":" - Those ones-> those one","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"Harvey seldom pays his bills on time, and his brother does too.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"pays his bills","b":"on time","c":"his","d":"does too","answer":"4","explain":" - Does too->does so\/does the same","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"The price of crude oil used to be a great deal lower than now, wasn't it?\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"price of","b":"great","c":"lower","d":"wasn't it","answer":"4","explain":" - Wasn't it-> didn't it","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"When an university formulates new regulations, it must relay its decision to the students and faculty.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"an","b":"new regulations","c":"it","d":"must relay its","answer":"1","explain":" - An-> a","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"Jim was upset last night because he had to do too many homeworks.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"upset","b":"because","c":"had to do","d":"many homeworks","answer":"4","explain":" - Many homeworks-> much homework","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"There is some scissors in the desk drawer in the bedroom if you need them.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"is","b":"scissors","c":"in","d":"in","answer":"1","explain":" - Is-> are","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"The Board of Realtors doesn't have any informations about the increase in rent for this area.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"informations","b":"about","c":"increase","d":"in rent for","answer":"1","explain":" - Informations-> information","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"}]}